

Farhat Ben Abdessamad

Date of birth: 07/24/1991 | **Nationality:** Tunisian | (+ 216) 52421629 |

farhat.benabdessamad@fsegt.utm.tn I | Box post koutine 2, Medenine, Tunisia 4121

I present myself:

Motivated student in development economics, I have experience in carrying out activities in the field of "research in migration and local development" acquired in various internships and training, as well as in the field of international trade. With a great ability to adapt, I know how to be proactive and reliable in carrying out my missions.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

01/07/2021 - now - Tunis, Tunisia

SALES MANAGER, – GraumaG, remote work, münchen / germany

- Ongoing mailbox monitoring.
- Respond to emails, particularly regarding purchase orders.
- Preparation of the list of products ready to be ordered.
- Control the goods sent by the manufacturer.
- Preparation of the list of products ready to be shipped.
- Verify that all files are saved under the portal.
- Control of the list of "BESTELLUNG" and materials in production.
- Creation of "Rechnung: Invoice + packing list + marking".
- Perform a continuous database update.
- Control of the arrival of goods in our warehouses.

09/01/2019 - 06/30/2021 - Tunis, Tunisia

STOCK MANAGEMENT MANAGER, – Cosmetics store, Tunis

- Manager.
- Leader.
- Cashier.
- Receipt of goods, control of delivery compliance, storage.
- Preparation of orders, packaging and palletization.
- Participation in the loading of trucks.
- Edition of administrative follow-up documents.

09/01/2018 -30/06/2019 - Tunis, Tunisia

INVESTIGATION AND DATA ENTRY AGENT - DESK STUDY MARKETING CONSULTING, Tunis

- Participation in the preparatory phase of the study in connection with the research team: evaluation of the effectiveness of the grids and questionnaires before the launch of the survey, proposal of areas for improvement.
- Preparation of the survey: methodology, instructions and materials available for recording the data collected, planning of the intervention and identification of the target people (age, sex, sociological category, etc.).
- Identification of response anomalies on the questionnaires (absence, overrun, illegibility), claim for modification or deletion of the study.
- Face-to-face field surveys: completion of a questionnaire with an average completion time of 1 to 2 months or more.
- Coding and data entry.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

30/11/2022: Doctoral thesis submission – Faculty of Economics and Management of Tunis, BP 248, Tunisia

DOCTORAL THESIS IN ECONOMIC SCIENCE "MIGRATION AND LOCAL DEVELOPMENT"

Faculty of economics and management of Tunis El manar

https://fsegt.rnu.tn/

09/15/2014 - 01/12/2017 - Faculty of Economics and Management of Tunis, BP 248, Tunisia

RESEARCH MASTERS IN DEVELOPMENT ECONOMICS

Faculty of economics and management of Tunis El manar

https://fseqt.rnu.tn/

09/15/2011 - 06/30/2014 - Faculty of Economics and Management of Tunis, BP 248, Tunisia

FUNDAMENTAL LICENSE IN BUSINESS ECONOMY

- Faculty of economics and management of Tunis El manar

https://fseqt.rnu.tn/

09/15/2010 - 06/30/2011 - Road of Gabès, Medenin, Tunisia

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN EXPERIMENTAL SCIENCES

"Gabès road" secondary school in Medenine

01/09/2020 - 30/10/2020 - Carr. of San Vicente of the Raspeig, s/n ,, Alicante, Spain

RESEARCH INTERNSHIP

University of Alicante (Spain)

https://www.ua.es

- Special attention paid to task planning and scheduling.
- Expert use of STATA and SPSS software for my academic research on local development and migration.
- Ability to clearly define the problems encountered and to identify the causes.

09/01/2019 - 30/11/2019 - Carr. of San Vicente of the Raspeig, s/n ,, Alicante, Spain

RESEARCH INTERNSHIP

University of Alicante (Spain)

https://www.ua.es/

- Synthesis skills, respect for grammar and spelling rules.
- Particular attention paid to the planning of tasks and the establishment of schedules.
- Integration of technological and digital innovations, ability to quickly acquire new knowledge.
- Sharing ideas and opinions with collaborators by taking advantage of each person's strengths.

06/01/2013 - 30/10/2013 - Box postal not 62 Medenin perseverance 4127 Medenin, Tunisia

SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT INTERNSHIP

Association: Medenine Strategic Development Center (CSDM)

- Ability to identify difficulties and make decisions individually or by consensus.
- Particular attention paid to their task planning and scheduling.
- Integration of technological and digital innovations, ability to quickly acquire new knowledge.
- Development of prospecting on the predefined geographical area, in collaboration with all the teams.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

LANGUAGES) native(s): ARABIC

Others) language(s): FRENCH and ENGLISH

	COMPREHENSION		ORAL EXPRESSION	WRITTEN
	Oral Comprehension	understanding Writing		
ARABIC	C1	C1	C1	C1
FRENCH	B2	B2	B2	B2
ENGLISH	B1	B1	B1	B1

Levels: A1 and A2: user of base; B1 and B2: user independent; C1 and C2: user experimented

DRIVER'S LICENSE

Driver's license: B **Driver's license:** C